{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947006996661","data":{"timestamp":" 947006996661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007003822","data":{"timestamp":" 947007003822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007013495","data":{"timestamp":" 947007013494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007027154","data":{"timestamp":" 947007027153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007033826","data":{"timestamp":" 947007033826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007042376","data":{"timestamp":" 947007042375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007063850","data":{"timestamp":" 947007063850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" a7deb2ff-4360-4cc7-ab70-92bc93cb79a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007072717","data":{"timestamp":" 947007072715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007072954","data":{"timestamp":" 947007072953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007073929","data":{"timestamp":" 947007073929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007075215","data":{"timestamp":" 947007075214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007078124","data":{"timestamp":" 947007078124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007078982","data":{"timestamp":" 947007078981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007079302","data":{"timestamp":" 947007079302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007080548","data":{"timestamp":" 947007080547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007084155","data":{"timestamp":" 947007084155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007085152","data":{"timestamp":" 947007085151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007085413","data":{"timestamp":" 947007085412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007086373","data":{"timestamp":" 947007086373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007089285","data":{"timestamp":" 947007089284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007089619","data":{"timestamp":" 947007089618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007089687","data":{"timestamp":" 947007089687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" 0f70cb35-360b-43bb-8218-20dd3bf8c0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007102481","data":{"timestamp":" 947007102480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007103048","data":{"timestamp":" 947007103048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007108856","data":{"timestamp":" 947007108856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007115767","data":{"timestamp":" 947007115767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007122798","data":{"timestamp":" 947007122797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007123953","data":{"timestamp":" 947007123953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" START_ANAHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007128664","data":{"timestamp":" 947007128663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007132182","data":{"timestamp":" 947007132181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007136616","data":{"timestamp":" 947007136615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007137869","data":{"timestamp":" 947007137869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007141444","data":{"timestamp":" 947007141444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007150715","data":{"timestamp":" 947007150715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007158161","data":{"timestamp":" 947007158161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007163113","data":{"timestamp":" 947007163113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007165813","data":{"timestamp":" 947007165812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007168733","data":{"timestamp":" 947007168732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007173538","data":{"timestamp":" 947007173538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007178670","data":{"timestamp":" 947007178670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007186258","data":{"timestamp":" 947007186258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007191019","data":{"timestamp":" 947007191019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007194794","data":{"timestamp":" 947007194794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007198603","data":{"timestamp":" 947007198603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007203292","data":{"timestamp":" 947007203292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007205542","data":{"timestamp":" 947007205542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007208966","data":{"timestamp":" 947007208965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007223161","data":{"timestamp":" 947007223161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007227973","data":{"timestamp":" 947007227973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007230497","data":{"timestamp":" 947007230497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007233623","data":{"timestamp":" 947007233622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007239024","data":{"timestamp":" 947007239024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007241328","data":{"timestamp":" 947007241328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007243416","data":{"timestamp":" 947007243415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007249988","data":{"timestamp":" 947007249987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007257835","data":{"timestamp":" 947007257835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007259968","data":{"timestamp":" 947007259968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007262111","data":{"timestamp":" 947007262110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007264128","data":{"timestamp":" 947007264128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007266453","data":{"timestamp":" 947007266452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007267962","data":{"timestamp":" 947007267961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" START_WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007268797","data":{"timestamp":" 947007268797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007271598","data":{"timestamp":" 947007271597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007274808","data":{"timestamp":" 947007274807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007279510","data":{"timestamp":" 947007279510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007290420","data":{"timestamp":" 947007290420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007292140","data":{"timestamp":" 947007292140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947007292257","data":{"timestamp":" 947007292257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_202926"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}